askmrcreditcard.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy of AskMrCreditCard.com

Effective Date: March 15 , 2012

This privacy policy describes how Smart Finance LLC collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: www.askmrcreditcard.com . It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We collect personal information from you such as email address and date of birth.  
We use this information:  
For registration purposes  
To send you requested product or service information  
To send you a newsletter  
To respond to your questions and concerns  
To allow you to correspond with other members

We may also disclose your personal information as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request, if Smart Finance LLC is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information, to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

**Information Sharing**

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as forum hosting provider and email marketing. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

**Choice/Opt-Out**

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at contactus@askmrcreditcard.com .

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

**_Cookies_**  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a userâ��s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser.

**_Third Party Cookies_**  
The use of cookies by third parties is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies.

**_Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)_**  
Our third party tracking utility partner employs a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a userâ��s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customersâ�� personally identifiable information.

**_Log Files_**  
As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track usersâ�� movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

**_Flash LSOs_**  
We use local shared objects, also known as Flash cookies, to store your preferences such as volume control or high game score, or display content based upon what you view on our site to personalize your visit.

Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies click here:  
http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118

**Links to Other Web Sites**

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Smart Finance LLC. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit.

**Additional Policy Information**

**_Social Media (Features) and Widgets_**

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button [and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

**_Facebook Connect or other OpenID provider_**  
You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

**_Public Forums_**  
Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs, community forums or messaging service. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. Furthermore, your date of birth and age may be displayed in several places on the forum. You may change your display setting by going to Edit Profile. To request removal of your personal information from our blog, community forum or messaging, contact us at contactus@askmrcreditcard.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

**Access to Personally Identifiable Information**

If your personal information changes, you may correct, delete inaccuracies or update your information by emailing us at contactus@askmrcreditcard.com or by contacting by postal mail at the contact information listed below. If you no longer desire our service, you may have your account deleted by emailing us at the address above. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at above email address. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Notification of Privacy Policy Changes**

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**Contact Information**

You can contact us by writing or email us at the address below:  
Smart Finance LLC  
579 South Devon Avenue  
Wayne, PA, United States 19087  
Email: contactus@askmrcreditcard.com
